在ForecatsAdapter的bindView方法中我们必须便利
In the ForecastAdapter bindView method,
we have to traverse
视图层级来找到视图，以往里设置数据。
the view hierarchy to find the views
in order to set data onto them.
如果是一个回收的视图，
If it's a recycled view,
也就是说他之前在列表中被用来显示过其他数据，
meaning it's been used in the list
previously to display other data,
我们也还是需要遍历视图层级来找到所有视图。
we still have to traverse the view
hierarchy to find all the views.
要删除不必要的findViewById调用，
To remove unnecessary
findViewById calls,
我们可以使用ViewHolder模式。
we can use the View Holder Pattern.
对于一个包含了不同视图的列表项布局，
For a list item layout that
contains different views,
我们可以创建一个ViewHolder对象。
we can create a View Holder object.
他包含了指向布局中每一个视图的成员变量。
It contains member variables that
reference each View in the layout.
ViewHolder对象存在视图的Tag域中。
The View Holder object is stored
in the tag field of the View.
下一次视图被回收利用时，
The next time that
the View is recycled and
我们只要直接把数据设进这些域中。
used again, we can just immediately
set the data on to these fields.
你不必再去找一遍所有视图了。
You don't have to go
find all the views again.
这是我们的ViewHolder类。
This is our ViewHolder class.
你可以将它命名为任何你喜欢的。
You can name it anything you want.
他只是一个Java类
It's just a Java class.
给到列表项布局，我们执行所有的findViewById调用。
Given the list item layout,
we do all the findViewById calls.
这样我们可以持有所有子视图的引用。
That way we can hold references
to all the child views.
在newView方法中，当我们加载视图之后，
In the newView method after
we've inflated the view,
我们根据此视图创建一个新的viewHolder对象。
we create a new viewHolder
object from that view.
然后我们将那个viewHolder作为view的tag。
Then we set that viewHolder
as the tag of the view.
tag可以被用来存放任何对象。
The tag can be used to store any object.
但不要滥用，因为当你从中读取时，
But don't abuse it because
when you read it back you,
必须知道你在那儿存了写什么。
have to know what you stored in there.
然后在适配器的bindView调用中，
Then in the adaptor bindView call,
我们从tag中读取viewHolder对象。
we read from the tag to get
back the viewHolder object.
现在我们立刻得到了对我们需要更新的所有独立视图的引用
Now we immediately have references to
all the individual views that we need to
例如iconView，dateView，descriptionView等等。
update, such as icon view, date view,
description view and so on.